IÐUNN PÁLSDÓTTIR

STUDENT



CONTACTS

(+354) 8541700	<
idunnpals98@gmail.com	\succeq
Sjafnargata, Reykjavík, 101, Iceland	0

SKILLS
Python
Java
Matlab
R
SQL
Inventor
Autocad
Solidworks
Ansys
HTML
LANGUAGES
Icelandic

English

Norwegian

German

ABOUT ME

I enjoy working, meeting new people and new experiences. I try to challenge myself whenever I get the chance, for example by sitting on boards in student associations, traveling to foreign countries or spending time on subjects that I struggle with. The year of 2019 | traveled to Asia where | stayed for four months. The trip began in India where | spent one month with my friend. After a month in India I traveled alone through Nepal and southeast Asia. I look forward to new challenges which I will meet with experience I have gained, people I have gotten to know and people I am yet to meet.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Summer employee, Landsvirkjun (the National Power Company) Thjorsar area, Skeiða- og Gnúpverjahreppur

May 2021 - Aug 2021

Monitoring and registration of various equipment due to environmental issues, review and updates of job risk assessment of workers. Project concerning definition and preparation for a tender for contractors and more.

Elderly care, Fossahlíð Nursing home, Seyðisfjörður

May 2020 - Aug 2020

I moved to Seyðisfjörður where I cared for the elderly at the towns nursing home

Assistant, Fossvogur emergency room, Reykjavík

Jan 2019 - May 2020

Transportation of patients for tests as well as transportation between and inside different departments/wards. Cleaning and general patient care. Management of equipment inventory for the ward under supervision. During acute incidents my role, among other things, was to bring necessary equipment from the inventory.

Free lance contractor, Lambing in Fossnes, Skeiða- og Gnúpverjahreppur

May 2018 - Present

Day and night shifts during lambing season. Delivering lambs and other necessary farm work such as: making room for unborn lambs, marking lambs and more

Elderly care, Sóltún Nursing home, Reykjavík

Oct 2017 - May 2018

Cared for the elderly

Guide, Núpshestar horse rental, Skeiða- og Gnúpverjahreppur

May 2013 - Aug 2018

Tending to and assisting tourists during riding tours of differing lengths. Tours from one to three days with beginners and more experienced riders. Cleaning of riding gear, housekeeping, kitchen work as well as overseeing and running general operations between trips (planning etc.). Providing evening entertainment for tourists by singing, playing music and telling folk lore.

Assistant, Vestra Geldingaholt riding school, Skeiða- og Gnúpverjahreppur

May 2012 - Aug 2013

Assisting the riding teacher in coaching pupils how to be around horses, training them and taking care of them as well as taking care of riding gear. Kitchen work, housekeeping and entertainment for pupils after lessons

EDUCATION

High school diploma, Menntaskólinn við Hamrahlíð, Reykjavík

2017

Graduate from Menntaskólinn við Hamrahlíð junior college

Some College (no degree), FÍH music school, Reykjavík

Tónlistarskóli FÍH music school. Music theory graduate. I have also practiced on the accordion for ten years, three of which in FİH.

Bachelor of Science, University of Iceland, Reykjavík

Third year student in mechanical engineering in the School of natural sciences

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Information officer, The board of Vélin student association, Reykjavík

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022

Supervision of student association media as well as informing members of events, meetings etc. Organizing the annual festival of the student association. Communication with companies regarding funding among other things. Other undertakings.

Secretary, The board of Gjálp business development association, Reykjavík

Aug 2017 - Aug 2018